

Johnathan Frabetti

Main contacts

(14) 99897-1956 john.frabettiegmail.com

Social networks

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/john athan-frabetti-b04193207/
- https://www.youtube.com/@0xor

Address

Rua João Esteves de Souza, 755 - Bauru, São Paulo, Brasil

Interests

- Capture The Flag (CTF)
- Creation of tools and malware
- Teaching classes on Cybersecurity
- Making videos for YouTube about technology
- Creating cheats for online aames
- Conducting reverse engineering on programs to understand their functionalities
- Playing logical reasoning games

RESUME

With 3 years of experience in cybersecurity, I highlight my role as a specialized Pentest analyst. I have developed strong competencies in security testing, standing out in the identification and mitigation of vulnerabilities. I am actively seeking opportunities within companies that prioritize cybersecurity, aiming to apply my expertise in Pentesting to contribute to the effective growth and protection of digital assets.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

- Bachelor of Computer Science, Sagrado Coração University (USC), **2022 Present**;
- Computer Maintenance Technician, SENAI Bauru, 2019 -2020:
- Systems Development Technician, SENAI Bauru, 2020 -2021.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Internship in Analysis and Development of Protheus ERP, TOTVS, 2021 - 2021.

- Worked collaboratively on the development of routines for Protheus:
- Acquired and applied knowledge in TL++ and Fluig BPM;
- Assisted in the maintenance of TOTVS infrastructure.

Cyber Security Analyst, NTT DATA , 2021 - 2023

- Implemented defense systems such as WAZUH and CrowdStrike Falcon XDR;
- Delivered training sessions on Secure Development Lifecycle (AppSec);
- Conducted Web and Mobile Pentests on critical applications in the financial and telecommunications sectors, collaborating with renowned organizations such as Bradesco and TIM

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Skills: C/C++, Assembly x86, Python, Bash Scripting e PowerShell;
- CyberSecurity Skills: BurpSuite, Kali Linux, IDA Pro, JD-GUI e OllyDBG.
- **Teaching Skills:** Effective Communication, Adaptation and Educational Technology.

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: Native

English: Technical

• Japonese: Basic